thinkbabynames.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Think Baby Names

Think Baby Names is a baby names site committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of ThinkBabyNames.com. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

## What cookies are and how they are used

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, ThinkBabyNames.com may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Some features of ThinkBabyNames.com require that you accept cookies in order to work properly. 

Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes: 

(1) To identify and label all "favorite" baby names you selected since your last visit to the site. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you on this Web site, other sites, and other forms of media. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

ThinkBabyNames.com may also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. 

## How your information is used

The primary goal of ThinkBabyNames.com in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout ThinkBabyNames.com. 

## Who is collecting your information

When you are asked for personal information on ThinkBabyNames.com, you are sharing that information with ThinkBabyNames.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com). 

## With whom your information may be shared

As a general rule, ThinkBabyNames.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared. 

ThinkBabyNames.com may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of ThinkBabyNames.com or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of ThinkBabyNames.com, other users of ThinkBabyNames.com, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. ThinkBabyNames.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. 

## What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information

You have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services of ThinkBabyNames.com that require cookies in order to participate. These services include the saving of baby names to your "favorites" list. You can still use most of the features of ThinkBabyNames.com even if you do not accept cookies. 

ThinkBabyNames.com does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service. 

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [webmaster@thinkbabynames.com](mailto:webmaster@thinkbabynames.com).
